clueleads.com 2014-09-12

# mlm,India mlm news,mlm classifieds,India mlm companies,networker views,mlm articles,mlm directory,mlm software,Network marketing in Andhrapradesh,India

|  |   
---  

|  |  |    
---|---  
| This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. [clueleads.com](http://www.clueleads.com/) is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.   
---  
In our capacity as an interactive internet portal, we are required to collect information about you, including up-to-date, accurate and complete contact details. When you use one of our services with a form we ask for your full name, organization, country, e-mail address, and other relevant information to process your request. We may use this personally identifiable information to contact you about your members account or other matters relating to the service, such as to inform you about new features on our site. We may also use this personally identifiable information to send you our newsletter or e-mail messages regarding products or services we think you might be interested in.  
This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.  
   
We may disclose certain personal information as follows:  
To third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf, To law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or  
To legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.By having your mobile number listed on   
[clueleads.com](http://www.clueleads.com/), you agree to receive SMS from users who may wish to contact you through the site.  
Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.  
We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer.  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.  
This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.  
We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties.   
Corrections/Contact  
Users of this Site may contact [clueleads.com](http://www.clueleads.com/) to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to us and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, we will conduct an investigation into the matter, and we will take necessary measure/s to rectify the source of the complaint, as appropriate.  
   
|   
---
